

SUMMARY

Dedicated and efficient Full-stack Engineer with 2 years of industrial experience in MERN stack. I've always found coding intuitive and have pushed myself to learn the most effective ways to achieve a result. I can adapt to any technology rapidly making myself flexible upon any tech stack and can quickly integrate into a team, so I can provide value to the company and the customers.

CONTACT INFO

MOBILE: 0774 229 289

EMAIL: sandeepa8956@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

FRONT END:

React, JavaScript, Typescript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, SASS, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Redux-Saga, Ant Design, Material UI, Bootstrap, Auth0, Google Maps API

BACK END:

NodeJS, ExpressJS, REST API

DATABASES:

MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase

ADDITIONAL LANGUAGES:

Java, C#, C++, C, Python

VCS:

GitLab, GitHub

IDEs and TOOLS:

JEST, ESLint, Prettier, Adobe XD, Figma, Jira, VSCode, Intellij IDEA, Eclipse EE

KAVINDU S. LIYANAGE

Portfolio Website - www.kavindus.com

EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Engineer - CabbageApps

Jan 2022 to Present

FusionX - An Exponential Cloud Financial Suite

- ✓ Develop frontend with React-Typescript
- ✓ Working with Git for version controlling
- ✓ Working with Jira for agile development

Associate Full Stack Engineer - Orel IT

May 2021 to Dec 2021

Workwise – Online Marketplace for Financial Properties

- ✓ Develop frontend with React-Typescript
- ✓ Work with Google APIs to integrate Google map functionalities
- ✓ Working with Git for version controlling
- ✓ Working with Jira for agile development

Software Engineering Intern - Orel IT

Nov 2020 to Apr 2021

Hommazze – Online Quotation Generating Web app for Contractors

- ✓ Develop frontend with React-Typescript
- ✓ Develop backend with Express-NodeJS
- ✓ Working with Git for version controlling
- ✓ Working with Jira for agile development

EDUCATION

Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology (SLIIT)

BSc (Hons) in Information Technology Specializing in Software Engineering - Nov 2017 to Dec 2021

Rahula College Matara

GCE Advanced Level - 2017 (Index No. 5976278)

- / ICT C
- ✓ Combined Math S
- ✓ Physics S

GCE Ordinary Level - 2014 (Index No. 41751850)

✓ 7 - "A" passes, 1 - "B" pass, 1 - "C" pass.

PROJECTS

• FusionX - Lending Web App

Description:

FusionX is a core-banking platform developed to help standardize and optimize the operations of the branches.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Development of Breadcrumb navigation, OD Appraisal creation, Guarantor Details Management, Income & Expenses Analysis, Loan Calculation, Lead Creation, and Current Account Management. Involved in the process of bug fixing and hotfixes.

Technologies:

React with TypeScript, Redux-toolkit, Ant-Design, Tailwind CSS, Styled-components, Auth0

WEBSITES AND SOCIAL LINKS

GITHUB:

github.com/KavinduLiyanage

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com/in/kavinduliyanage

PORTFOLIO:

www.kavindus.com

MEDIUM:

medium.com/@KavinduLiyanage

BLOG:

<u>kavinduliyanage.wixsite.com/techpurs</u> <u>ue</u>

PERSONAL INFO

FULL NAME:

Kavindu Sandeepa Liyanage

NIC: 981682629V

DOB: 16th June 1998

GENDER: Male

MARITAL STATUS: Single

ADDRESS:

'Sandeepa', Hediwatta, Waralla,

Matara.

REFEREES

Mr. Chamith K. Ranaweera

Tech Lead

CabbageApps (Pvt) Ltd

Email: chamith@cabbageapps.com

Mobile: +94 77 352 3896

Mr. Adeesha Savinda de Silva

Senior Solutions Engineer

WSO2 Lanka (Pvt) Ltd

Email: adeesha@wso2.com Mobile: +94 76 354 0500

Workwise Web App with Admin Panel (Orel IT)

Description:

Workwise is an online marketplace that connects people who want to rent out their properties, office listing with people who are looking for properties in that locale. For owners and affiliates participating in Workwise is a way to earn income from their property.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Development of property searching function, Google map viewing function, property adding function, multiple images uploading function, property contract signing function, reserved properties viewing function, analytics functions of admin panel and property management functions of admin panel.

Involved in the process of bug fixing and hotfixes.

Technologies:

ReactJS, Redux, Redux-saga, Google API, Material UI, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, AWS EC2, S3, Formik

• Online Fashion Store App (Personal)

Description:

Web Application for Online Fashion Store. MERN Stack E-commerce web application.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Add Products with Details(Images). Retrieve all Products Details in Card view with Image Slider. Edit, Update and Delete Products. Manage Discounts. Main Search in Navigation panel. Quick Search. Filter by price range, branch availability, and categories.

All images related works.

Technologies:

ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB Atlas, Heroku, GitHub Source Code:

https://github.com/KavinduLiyanage/Fashion-Store

Deployment:

https://afternoon-beyond-91179.herokuapp.com/

• Timetable Management System (Personal)

Description:

Desktop application for creating the timetables in university.

Roles and Responsibilities:

All lecturers related works. All subjects related works. All Sessions related works.

Technologies:

C#, .Net Framework, Azure Database

Source Code:

https://github.com/KavinduLiyanage/Timetable-Management-System

Hemas Health App Redesign (Personal)

Description:

Redesign the existing Hemas Health app. Matches the application color theme and company color theme. Made consistency between all interfaces, header, and bottom navbar.

Roles and Responsibilities:

Main Dashboard, Order Medicine Function, Lab Repots Function.

Technologies:

Flutter and Adobe XD

Source Code:

https://github.com/KavinduLiyanage/Hemas-Health-App